<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AAAIMX | Student Chapter</title>
    <description>We are a group of students and researchers from the ITM along with researchers from the Center for Mathematical Research (CIMAT) and CentroGeo</description>
    <link>http://aaaimx.org/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://aaaimx.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>GitHub Campus Experts 🚩</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/1790822/28984617-e789fa78-792c-11e7-9c9f-17c23a70e6cc.png&quot; alt=&quot;lockup&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-is-a-campus-expert&quot;&gt;What is a Campus Expert?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People learn better when they can learn with a community of likeminded peers. A Campus Expert is a student trained to build a strong technical community, on campus. As well as training, Campus Experts have access to resources and support from GitHub, such as swag, sponsorship, and the opportunity to attend events like GitHub Universe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-do-i-become-a-campus-expert&quot;&gt;How do I become a Campus Expert?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To become a Campus Expert, you first have to complete the training. To join the training, you need to be a verified student, over the age of 18. To verify as a student, sign up for the &lt;a href=&quot;https://education.github.com/pack&quot;&gt;GitHub Student Developer Pack&lt;/a&gt;. Once you are verified as a student, you can join the &lt;a href=&quot;https://education.github.com/experts&quot;&gt;Campus Expert training&lt;/a&gt; ✨.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;what-benefits-do-campus-experts-get-from-github&quot;&gt;What benefits do Campus Experts get from GitHub?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you complete the training and become a Campus Expert, you have access to benefits and extra support from GitHub.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Campus Expert benefits depend on the training modules completed. Each training module awards access to a different set of related benefits, described in the README of the training module. As a Campus Expert completes more training modules, they will gain access to more resources to use to help their community. Benefits range from free stickers and cheat sheets for your school, to event/hackathon sponsorships, to travel support to attend GitHub events and conferences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to material resources and benefits, Campus Experts gain access to regular webinars and guest talks from industry experts, and spaces to collaborate with other Campus Experts and GitHubbers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-does-being-a-campus-expert-work-what-are-the-expectations-of-a-campus-expert&quot;&gt;How does being a Campus Expert work? What are the expectations of a Campus Expert?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the introductory part of the training, you analyse your community and define goals for improving it. As a Campus Expert, you are expected to meet these goals, and build the best community for your campus. We at GitHub understand that you are busy students, trying to make your campus a better place. This is why you set your own community goals, and participate in as much of the training as you need to achieve those goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you become a Campus Expert, you gain access to tools that help you make resource requests, and collaborate with GitHub Staff and other Campus Experts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;do-i-need-to-know-how-to-use-gitgithub&quot;&gt;Do I need to know how to use Git/GitHub?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Campus Experts is about &lt;em&gt;your community&lt;/em&gt;, not becoming a Git master. However, Campus Experts and the training does primarily take place through GitHub, so some Git/GitHub knowledge is helpful. You can learn everything you need to complete the training &lt;a href=&quot;https://services.github.com/on-demand/intro-to-github/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://aaaimx.org/blog/campus-experts</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://aaaimx.org/blog/campus-experts</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Github Student Developer Pack</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;There’s no substitute for hands-on experience. But for most students, real world tools can be cost-prohibitive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive feature-image&quot; src=&quot;https://dwa5x7aod66zk.cloudfront.net/assets/sdp-backpack-a64038716bf134f45e809ff86b9611fb97e41bbd2ccfa3181da73cf164d3c200.png&quot; style=&quot;display:none&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;learn-to-ship-software-like-a-pro&quot;&gt;Learn to ship software like a pro.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s why we created the GitHub Student Developer Pack with some of our partners and friends: to give students free access to the best developer tools in one place so they can learn by doing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before you receive access to the offers, we’ll need to verify that you are a student.
Teachers, researchers, faculty, and staff are not eligible for the Pack, but can get free and discounted access to GitHub.
Navigate to this link to more details. &lt;a href=&quot;https://education.github.com/pack#offers&quot;&gt;View on GitHub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://aaaimx.org/blog/developer-pack</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://aaaimx.org/blog/developer-pack</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
